<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome! on Viel Losero&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome! on Viel Losero&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>es</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 11:34:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox privacity: Configuration and script.</title>
      <link>/en/posts/5-firefox-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/posts/5-firefox-privacy/</guid>
      <description>Setting. Today to navigate with a little of privacy we can: Use a text browser like linx without features like java, videos, css, &amp;hellip;, use torbrowser, or configure firefox to navigate as safely and privately as possible.
Backup. The first thing we have to do to avoid losing our data is a copy of our firefox profile, it is under the user directory.
~/.mozilla/firefox/xxxxxxxx.default  root@kali:~# cp .mozilla/firefox/l50cihg0.default .mozilla/firefox/l50cihg0.default.bkp We could also copy only the files that interest us as bookmarks or history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>/en/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 10:47:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/support/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for yout support.
There are mani ways you can support:
 Help simply with a link or retweet to the articles.
 Share information on this site with others, spread the word.
 If you want to support this site with a donation, here is our Bitcoin address:
1LMJZcpJiHkiYiHrqUZdmbHJyUvF5KUsdq
All donations are appreciated!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using GPG: Gnu Privacy Guard.</title>
      <link>/en/posts/4-create-a-gpg-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 10:06:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/posts/4-create-a-gpg-key/</guid>
      <description>Creation of public and private keys To create the GPG keys we can use **gpg &amp;ndash;generate-key ** or **gpg &amp;ndash;full-generate-key ** the first command will create the keys without asking other options than necessary. If we want more control over some options such as size or validity period we will use **gpg &amp;ndash;full-generate-key **.
The size of the key is related to its security but also to the performance since it has to process with larger numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Static site generator: Script to generate the initial configuration.</title>
      <link>/en/posts/3-hugo-script-basic-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 12:22:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/posts/3-hugo-script-basic-site/</guid>
      <description>Script Code This script has helped me to generate mi website at initial moment since for me it was a bit awkward to editing all the files one by one to tests and see results of Hugo&amp;rsquo;s configuration . With this script we have all the initial configuration in a single file to be able to make configuration tests with Hugo relatively easy.
hugo-script-create-basic-site.sh
Testing the script Download root@kali:~# wget https://raw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Static site generator: Hosting on github.</title>
      <link>/en/posts/2-hosting-hugo-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 19:54:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/posts/2-hosting-hugo-on-github/</guid>
      <description>Github account After my previous post where I start with Hugo the creation of a web page with static content, now it&amp;rsquo;s time to host that page in github.
I will not go into how to create an account on github, you can follow the instructions to create the account from this link. Hosting on github
Once the github account has been created, the ssh key has been added for remote management and the repository has been created, we will create the submodule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 18:03:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Viel Losero is a pen name. If you can find me maybe you can hire me.
Why a pen name? Many reputable websites, researchers, and security experts use a “pen name” to protect their safety and privacy.
Mi rules:(Know as VLR - Viel Losero Rules or KiKoDoCo rules).
 Keep it simply, independent, honest, secure and free.
 Keep out ads, trackers, sponsors, &amp;hellip;
 Do Full transparency, best practices, ethical hacking, do not track &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 10:47:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email: viel.losero@gmail.com
Twitter: @VLosero
GitHub: VielLosero
PGP: 1418 39E8 065C 95F4 8E8D C329 F878 16F5 B769 CD83</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Static site generator: Starting with Hugo.</title>
      <link>/en/posts/1-hugo-start-how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 14:44:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/posts/1-hugo-start-how-to/</guid>
      <description>Why Hugo I chose hugo after comparing the top static site gen and reading a couple of posts by jekyll vs hugo, everyone will have their preferences. This is the first SSG I use since for some I had to start, Hugo&amp;rsquo;s documentation is quite broad and easy to understand.
Hugo installation Installing Hugo will depend on the operating system we have. In Devian it is as easy as using apt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>